# JOSE NARDULLI

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Argentina

11-51649239

iosenardulli@gmail.com

## **ABOUT**

Throughout my career, the subjects I found most interesting are Backend Development, Databases, Software Engineering, and Data Analysis. Most of my experience comes from self-taught lessons and courses in languages such as Python, C#, JavaScript, working in related projects as web administrative API and working on personal projects while completing diverse courses online that I found helpful. I have also developed test plans for testing software to expose flaws in various programs as well as collaborating with my colleagues in agile settings to ensure that the quality of the system meets the standard before release

## EDUCATION —

# Systems Engineer **Universidad Bicentenaria** de Aragua Venezuela 2008-2013

#### EXPERIENCE

January 2023 - Current Full Stack Developer • Solutica S.R.L. October 2021 - October 2022 JavaScript Developer • Associated • J.P. Morgan Chase September 2019 - October 2021 Full Stack Developer • Solutica S.R.L. April 2018 - September 2019 PL-SQL Developer • Simply I.T.

# KEY SKILLS -

Programing languages:

C# 🗪

Java €

JavaScript JS

Python \*

HTML

css 😇

PL-SQL, TRANSACT, MySQL sql

Frameworks, Systems or libraries: ASP.NET, Entity Framework.

MVC, spring boot, spring data, hibernate/jpa JQuery, React, Redux, Hooks, Vue. node Numpy, Panda, Flask, Django, Pygame,

Skeleton, Bootstrap 4.0.

# COURSES AND SEMINARS

**Programacion Web Full Stack Digital House Academy** 

Expedición: mar. 2023

Aptitudes: Desarrollo Full Stack · Node.js · Sequelize.js · SQL · MySQL · React.js · Desarrollo de API

Python and Django Full Stack Web Developer Bootcamp Jose Portilla, Head of Data Science, Pierian Data Inc. 32hs

Python eCommerce | Build a Django eCommerce Web Application

Justin Mitchel, Coding Entrepreneur & Teacher. 33hs

React - La Guía Completa: Hooks Context Redux MERN +15 Apps Juan Pablo De la torre Valdez, 44hs

# ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

LinkedIn in: https://www.linkedin.com/in/jose-nardulli-75b29021b/

Github : https://github.com/Comrak

Portfolio : https://josenardulli.netlify.app/

#### LANGUAGES

Spanish (native), English (Advance), Italian (Intermediate)